[{"release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"area": {"id": "3e08b2cd-69f3-317c-b1e4-e71be581839e", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["MX"], "name": "Mexico", "sort-name": "Mexico"}, "date": "2004"}], "cover-art-archive": {"artwork": "true", "front": "true", "count": "1", "back": "false"}, "country": "MX", "quality": "normal", "id": "11aa512f-360c-403c-aaac-9b48cdcead9c", "title": "Con todo respeto", "status": "Official", "text-representation": {"language": "spa", "script": "Latn"}, "date": "2004"}, {"release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"area": {"id": "3e08b2cd-69f3-317c-b1e4-e71be581839e", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["MX"], "name": "Mexico", "sort-name": "Mexico"}, "date": "1999-10-04"}], "cover-art-archive": {"artwork": "true", "front": "true", "count": "1", "back": "false"}, "country": "MX", "packaging": "Jewel Case", "quality": "normal", "id": "20cb3097-6fc1-4942-9763-d5508f478dfd", "title": "Apocalypshit", "status": "Official", "text-representation": {"language": "spa", "script": "Latn"}, "date": "1999-10-04", "disambiguation": "Lenticular cover"}, {"release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"area": {"id": "3e08b2cd-69f3-317c-b1e4-e71be581839e", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["MX"], "name": "Mexico", "sort-name": "Mexico"}, "date": "1997-08-26"}], "quality": "normal", "country": "MX", "packaging": "Jewel Case", "asin": "B00002498N", "cover-art-archive": {"artwork": "true", "front": "true", "count": "20", "back": "true"}, "id": "300c1f51-f281-384b-9c1a-a933ee668aeb", "title": "\u00bfD\u00f3nde jugar\u00e1n las ni\u00f1as?", "status": "Official", "text-representation": {"language": "spa", "script": "Latn"}, "date": "1997-08-26", "barcode": "602557503128"}, {"release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"area": {"id": "89a675c2-3e37-3518-b83c-418bad59a85a", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["XE"], "name": "Europe", "sort-name": "Europe"}, "date": "1999-10-04"}], "quality": "normal", "country": "XE", "packaging": "Jewel Case", "asin": "B00002DE2O", "cover-art-archive": {"artwork": "true", "front": "true", "count": "1", "back": "false"}, "id": "365af3be-ad03-44bc-8920-52e978812d1d", "title": "Apocalypshit", "status": "Official", "text-representation": {"language": "spa", "script": "Latn"}, "date": "1999-10-04", "barcode": "601215387520"}, {"release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"area": {"id": "3e08b2cd-69f3-317c-b1e4-e71be581839e", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["MX"], "name": "Mexico", "sort-name": "Mexico"}, "date": "2014-06-24"}], "quality": "normal", "country": "MX", "packaging": "Digipak", "asin": "B00KL3TU2A", "cover-art-archive": {"artwork": "false", "front": "false", "count": "0", "back": "false"}, "id": "4ce2a7d6-305e-4cf9-bbe4-621620fd08ff", "title": "Agua maldita", "status": "Official", "text-representation": {"language": "spa", "script": "Latn"}, "date": "2014-06-24", "barcode": "602537849314"}, {"cover-art-archive": {"artwork": "false", "front": "false", "count": "0", "back": "false"}, "id": "4cff7e3f-9268-4e2b-b951-eccef623153b", "title": "Cocktail Party", "status": "Official", "quality": "normal", "text-representation": {"language": "spa", "script": "Latn"}}, {"release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"area": {"id": "3e08b2cd-69f3-317c-b1e4-e71be581839e", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["MX"], "name": "Mexico", "sort-name": "Mexico"}, "date": "1999-10-04"}], "cover-art-archive": {"artwork": "false", "front": "false", "count": "0", "back": "false"}, "country": "MX", "packaging": "Jewel Case", "quality": "normal", "id": "61981fa3-db63-43ce-a032-36d76ffbfd8b", "title": "Apocalypshit", "status": "Official", "text-representation": {"language": "spa", "script": "Latn"}, "date": "1999-10-04", "barcode": "601215377026"}, {"release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"area": {"id": "3e08b2cd-69f3-317c-b1e4-e71be581839e", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["MX"], "name": "Mexico", "sort-name": "Mexico"}, "date": "2014-06-20"}], "cover-art-archive": {"artwork": "false", "front": "false", "count": "0", "back": "false"}, "country": "MX", "asin": "B00KL3TU2A", "quality": "normal", "id": "61e2d850-46ab-44b7-beb8-9484424fed6e", "title": "Agua maldita", "status": "Official", "text-representation": {"language": "spa", "script": "Latn"}, "date": "2014-06-20"}, {"release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"area": {"id": "3e08b2cd-69f3-317c-b1e4-e71be581839e", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["MX"], "name": "Mexico", "sort-name": "Mexico"}, "date": "1998-11-24"}], "cover-art-archive": {"artwork": "false", "front": "false", "count": "0", "back": "false"}, "country": "MX", "asin": "B00000FCDU", "quality": "normal", "id": "6a97aeb8-e790-4932-95ca-c18c2e701775", "title": "Molomix", "status": "Official", "text-representation": {"language": "spa", "script": "Latn"}, "date": "1998-11-24"}, {"release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"area": {"id": "89a675c2-3e37-3518-b83c-418bad59a85a", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["XE"], "name": "Europe", "sort-name": "Europe"}, "date": "1999-10-02"}], "quality": "normal", "country": "XE", "packaging": "Jewel Case", "asin": "B00002DE2O", "cover-art-archive": {"artwork": "true", "front": "true", "count": "5", "back": "true"}, "id": "6ddbe78e-0632-47b4-b3b6-c4528265f6f0", "title": "Apocalypshit", "status": "Official", "text-representation": {"language": "spa", "script": "Latn"}, "date": "1999-10-02", "barcode": "601215387421"}, {"release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"area": {"id": "489ce91b-6658-3307-9877-795b68554c98", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["US"], "name": "United States", "sort-name": "United States"}, "date": "2008-07-01"}], "quality": "normal", "country": "US", "packaging": "Jewel Case", "asin": "B001AI1QYK", "cover-art-archive": {"artwork": "true", "front": "true", "count": "1", "back": "false"}, "id": "7a739c8e-587a-4a8a-984d-8d294f792afb", "title": "\u00bfD\u00f3nde jugar\u00e1n las ni\u00f1as?", "status": "Official", "text-representation": {"language": "spa", "script": "Latn"}, "date": "2008-07-01", "barcode": "602517746985", "disambiguation": "10th Anniversary Edition"}, {"release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"area": {"id": "3e08b2cd-69f3-317c-b1e4-e71be581839e", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["MX"], "name": "Mexico", "sort-name": "Mexico"}, "date": "2007-10-16"}], "cover-art-archive": {"artwork": "false", "front": "false", "count": "0", "back": "false"}, "country": "MX", "asin": "B000UZ4G5A", "quality": "normal", "id": "92be72f0-1908-4ec5-88ef-1f67bb25b312", "title": "Eternamiente", "status": "Official", "text-representation": {"language": "spa", "script": "Latn"}, "date": "2007-10-16", "barcode": "602517423596"}, {"release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"area": {"id": "2db42837-c832-3c27-b4a3-08198f75693c", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["JP"], "name": "Japan", "sort-name": "Japan"}, "date": "1999-10-20"}], "cover-art-archive": {"artwork": "false", "front": "false", "count": "0", "back": "false"}, "country": "JP", "asin": "B00003IQQX", "quality": "normal", "id": "93d2049e-b058-4b8d-bdd9-f5223a63daba", "title": "Apocalypshit", "status": "Official", "text-representation": {"language": "spa", "script": "Latn"}, "date": "1999-10-20", "barcode": "4988067041593"}, {"release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"area": {"id": "89a675c2-3e37-3518-b83c-418bad59a85a", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["XE"], "name": "Europe", "sort-name": "Europe"}, "date": "1999"}], "quality": "normal", "country": "XE", "packaging": "Jewel Case", "cover-art-archive": {"artwork": "false", "front": "false", "count": "0", "back": "false"}, "id": "9c42bc22-419e-4b7b-be65-0d484cf6c3a9", "title": "Apocalypshit", "status": "Official", "text-representation": {"language": "spa", "script": "Latn"}, "date": "1999", "barcode": "601215387520", "disambiguation": "Lenticular cover"}, {"release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"area": {"id": "02b60d8d-7164-339d-868d-22d147d9f74a", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["CO"], "name": "Colombia", "sort-name": "Colombia"}}], "cover-art-archive": {"artwork": "true", "front": "true", "count": "1", "back": "false"}, "country": "CO", "quality": "normal", "id": "9c6c4431-890f-41f7-82d1-2c3c624b1d68", "title": "Dance and Dense Denso", "status": "Bootleg", "text-representation": {"language": "spa", "script": "Latn"}}, {"release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"area": {"id": "3e08b2cd-69f3-317c-b1e4-e71be581839e", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["MX"], "name": "Mexico", "sort-name": "Mexico"}, "date": "2012"}], "cover-art-archive": {"artwork": "true", "front": "true", "count": "4", "back": "true"}, "country": "MX", "quality": "normal", "id": "a344134e-d87a-4fd8-addb-8eac275eb610", "title": "Desde Rusia con Amor", "status": "Official", "text-representation": {"language": "spa", "script": "Latn"}, "date": "2012", "barcode": "602537057610", "disambiguation": "Censored cover"}, {"release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"area": {"id": "3e08b2cd-69f3-317c-b1e4-e71be581839e", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["MX"], "name": "Mexico", "sort-name": "Mexico"}, "date": "2004-11-23"}], "cover-art-archive": {"artwork": "false", "front": "false", "count": "0", "back": "false"}, "country": "MX", "asin": "B000667H9U", "quality": "normal", "id": "c0da3134-8a0b-494f-8939-4234fc488e19", "title": "Con todo respeto", "status": "Official", "text-representation": {"language": "spa", "script": "Latn"}, "date": "2004-11-23", "barcode": "0602498250112"}, {"release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"area": {"id": "3e08b2cd-69f3-317c-b1e4-e71be581839e", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["MX"], "name": "Mexico", "sort-name": "Mexico"}, "date": "2003-05-26"}], "cover-art-archive": {"artwork": "true", "front": "true", "count": "3", "back": "true"}, "country": "MX", "packaging": "Jewel Case", "quality": "normal", "id": "ca90a458-54af-341b-8057-9f281774bdd0", "title": "Dance and Dense Denso", "status": "Official", "text-representation": {"language": "spa", "script": "Latn"}, "date": "2003-05-26", "barcode": "044006666129"}, {"release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"area": {"id": "471c46a7-afc5-31c4-923c-d0444f5053a4", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["ES"], "name": "Spain", "sort-name": "Spain"}, "date": "1997"}], "cover-art-archive": {"artwork": "true", "front": "true", "count": "3", "back": "true"}, "country": "ES", "quality": "normal", "id": "d3002d92-47b4-4a26-bea3-47302eaf5ca1", "title": "\u00bfD\u00f3nde jugar\u00e1n las ni\u00f1as?", "status": "Official", "text-representation": {"language": "spa", "script": "Latn"}, "date": "1997", "barcode": "602557503128"}, {"release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"area": {"id": "2db42837-c832-3c27-b4a3-08198f75693c", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["JP"], "name": "Japan", "sort-name": "Japan"}, "date": "1998-09-23"}], "cover-art-archive": {"artwork": "false", "front": "false", "count": "0", "back": "false"}, "country": "JP", "asin": "B00000G6IC", "quality": "normal", "id": "d72b14b8-f34e-4398-9ac3-7c4b929f6e1a", "title": "\u00bfD\u00f3nde jugar\u00e1n las ni\u00f1as?", "status": "Official", "text-representation": {"language": "spa", "script": "Latn"}, "date": "1998-09-23", "barcode": "4988067035042"}, {"release-event-count": 2, "release-event-list": [{"area": {"id": "489ce91b-6658-3307-9877-795b68554c98", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["US"], "name": "United States", "sort-name": "United States"}, "date": "2012-07-08"}, {"area": {"id": "3e08b2cd-69f3-317c-b1e4-e71be581839e", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["MX"], "name": "Mexico", "sort-name": "Mexico"}, "date": "2012"}], "cover-art-archive": {"artwork": "true", "front": "true", "count": "1", "back": "false"}, "country": "US", "quality": "normal", "id": "db529ddc-4701-4fb4-802b-3fcc3967f33c", "title": "Desde Rusia con amor", "status": "Official", "text-representation": {"language": "spa", "script": "Latn"}, "date": "2012-07-08", "barcode": "602537050147"}, {"release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"area": {"id": "89a675c2-3e37-3518-b83c-418bad59a85a", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["XE"], "name": "Europe", "sort-name": "Europe"}, "date": "1999"}], "cover-art-archive": {"artwork": "false", "front": "false", "count": "0", "back": "false"}, "country": "XE", "asin": "B000023Y13", "quality": "normal", "id": "e43e50b8-1e9e-3b89-9a22-1db995c5992d", "title": "\u00bfD\u00f3nde jugar\u00e1n las ni\u00f1as?", "status": "Official", "text-representation": {"language": "spa", "script": "Latn"}, "date": "1999", "barcode": "602438058723"}, {"release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"area": {"id": "525d4e18-3d00-31b9-a58b-a146a916de8f", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["XW"], "name": "[Worldwide]", "sort-name": "[Worldwide]"}, "date": "2008-07-01"}], "quality": "normal", "country": "XW", "packaging": "None", "asin": "B001BGY80A", "cover-art-archive": {"artwork": "true", "front": "true", "count": "1", "back": "false"}, "id": "f11e5894-65b6-4bf5-9680-d89aa4af196c", "title": "\u00bfD\u00f3nde jugar\u00e1n las ni\u00f1as?", "status": "Official", "text-representation": {"language": "spa", "script": "Latn"}, "date": "2008-07-01", "barcode": "", "disambiguation": "10th Anniversary Edition"}, {"release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"area": {"id": "489ce91b-6658-3307-9877-795b68554c98", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["US"], "name": "United States", "sort-name": "United States"}, "date": "2003-02-25"}], "cover-art-archive": {"artwork": "false", "front": "false", "count": "0", "back": "false"}, "country": "US", "asin": "B00008BRCY", "quality": "normal", "id": "f36366fb-3c8b-4908-8ef1-aae50a55ce38", "title": "Dance and Dense Denso", "status": "Official", "text-representation": {"language": "spa", "script": "Latn"}, "date": "2003-02-25"}, {"release-event-count": 1, "release-event-list": [{"area": {"id": "3e08b2cd-69f3-317c-b1e4-e71be581839e", "iso-3166-1-code-list": ["MX"], "name": "Mexico", "sort-name": "Mexico"}, "date": "2012"}], "cover-art-archive": {"artwork": "true", "front": "true", "count": "3", "back": "true"}, "country": "MX", "quality": "normal", "id": "f8281922-d273-4b6f-8a61-c5de53e2b4a4", "title": "Desde Rusia con amor", "status": "Official", "text-representation": {"language": "spa", "script": "Latn"}, "date": "2012", "barcode": "602537050154"}]